

About me

I am a senior software engineer currently based in Brno, Czech republic.

My primary field is development of front-end for web applications. I focus especially on architecture of the code-base and quality of it's design. What differs me from others is my multi-disciplined approach to work.

Besides development, I have experience with graphic design, product analysis and project management. I like to explore new technologies and I'm always for a good team-work.

Follow me

in in/jakubsoltes

jake-daniels

Reference

Pavel Šafařík

Project Manager @ ROI Hunter

pavel@roihunter.com +420 728 412 370

Filip Hyža

Project Manager & Analyst @ inQool

filip.hyza@gmail.com +420 605 346 343

Language

SK CZ ΕN

FR

DK \bullet

Jakub Soltés

web front-end developer



Brno, Czech republic



+420 733 533 220



jakub@jakubsoltes.com

Work experience

ROI Hunter

Nov 2016 - present Brno, Czech republic

Senior Front-end Developer

- development of key product features
- · design of software architecture
- responsibility for product's lifecycle and continuous integration
- collaboration across teams (back-end / front-end / UX / QA)
- JavaScript (ES8), TypeScript, React, Redux

Feb 2014 - Sep 2016 Brno, Czech republic

Front-end Developer & Product Analyst

- analysis of product ideas
- data modeling and design of software architecture
- · development of key product features
- roadmap planning, prioritization of features
- occasional graphic design
- JavaScript (ES6), React, Redux

i-Inventions

Mar 2011 - Oct 2013 Brno, Czech republic

Software Developer

- development of desktop applications
- data modeling, design of software architecture
- C#, .NET, WPF, XAML

Celebrio Software

May 2010 - Feb 2011 Brno. Czech republic

repu'bli:k

Dec 2009 - Feb 2010 Brno, Czech republic

Software Developer

- development of web application
- HTML, CSS, PHP, C#

Development Supporter

- PHP development
- documentation writing

Education

Masaryk University

Brno University of

Sep 2014 - Jun 2016 Brno, Czech republic

Technology

Sep 2009 - Jun 2013

Brno, Czech republic

Faculty of Informatics

Master's degree

Thesis

Service Science, Management and Enginering Analysis, optimization and implementation of technological processes in the stock market system ARTEX500.

Faculty of Information Technology

Bachelor's degree

Information Technology

Application for tree stability measurement.

Skills





React



HTML5









Git / GitHub



JavaScript / TypeScript

Adobe Photoshop

Hobbies













BADMINTON

DRAWING

SWING DANCING